[{"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小白"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "title": "浅蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小黄"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [4, 3], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小明"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小红"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [0, 2], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小白"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "title": "深蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小黄"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [4, 3], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小白"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "title": "浅蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小黄"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [4, 3], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小明"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "title": "浅蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小红"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [0, 2], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小白"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "title": "浅蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小黄"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [4, 3], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小明"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "title": "浅蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小红"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [0, 2], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小明"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "title": "棕色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小红"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [0, 2], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小明"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "title": "浅蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小红"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [0, 2], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小白"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "title": "深蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "title": "棕色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小黄"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [4, 3], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小白"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "title": "深蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小黄"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [4, 3], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小明"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "title": "棕色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小红"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [0, 2], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小明"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小红"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [0, 2], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小白"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "title": "深蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小黄"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [4, 3], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小明"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "title": "棕色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小红"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [0, 2], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小白"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小黄"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [4, 3], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小明"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "title": "浅蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "title": "深蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "title": "浅蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小红"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [0, 2], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小白"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg", "title": "棕色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小黄"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [4, 3], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小明"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "title": "浅蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "title": "红色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "左边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小红"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [0, 2], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}, {"body": [{"title": "选一选", "stem": "根据要求选一选", "content": ["v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_4.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_3.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_2.svg"], "inputList": [[{"type": "text", "value": "（1）"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小白"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子在"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_1.svg", "title": "浅蓝色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "，"}, {"type": "text", "value": "把它选出来。"}], [{"type": "text", "value": "（2）"}, {"type": "img", "value": "v2/通用/服饰/饰品/帽子/帽子_5.svg", "title": "黄色帽子"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "右边"}, {"type": "text", "value": "是"}, {"type": "keyword", "value": "小黄"}, {"type": "text", "value": "的帽子，把它选出来。"}]], "type": "pos-sequence-mulSelect"}], "answers": [4, 3], "knowledges": ["认识左右"], "resource": "resource", "type": "选择", "explain": "explain", "level": "2", "number": "1-5-3-08"}]